<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Faster Game Loading - Continued</name>
  <author>綠菇</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>Taranchuk.FasterGameLoading</packageId>
  <description>
Source: https://github.com/Taranchuk/FasterGameLoading
This fork: https://github.com/mushroomTW/FasterGameLoading---Continued.git

=== Does loading take forever? This mod is for you! ===

Sick of staring at the loading screen every time you start RimWorld? This mod cuts down startup time using several tricks that work in the background, so the game loads faster without changing any gameplay.

--- What it does ---

- Starts loading mod content earlier, during moments the game would otherwise sit idle.
- Optionally delays non-essential textures (like background objects) until after you enter a game — weapons, clothing, food, pawns, and furniture are always loaded right away so nothing looks broken. (disabled by default)
- Smarter atlas baking: by default, uses RimWorld's original baking process. When enabled, automatically adjusts batch sizes based on your GPU speed to reduce loading hitches. Enabling this is optional but recommended for high mod counts. (disabled by default)
- Texture downscaler: reduces the file size of high-resolution textures to save VRAM and speed up loading. Your original mod files are never touched — downscaled copies are stored in a separate folder, and you can delete them anytime to go back to full quality. (disabled by default)

--- Things to know ---

- The game may briefly freeze or feel unresponsive during startup. This is normal — the mod is doing work in the background.
- When first entering a game with delayed texture loading enabled, some objects may briefly show as pink/grey placeholders. They fill in within a few seconds.
- The texture downscaler and atlas baking options are optional. Atlas baking always runs in some form — disabling the option just uses the vanilla baking process instead of the adaptive one.

--- Works well with ---

- Loading Progress
- DefLoadCache
- Image Opt

--- Works best with a lot of mods. Zero impact on gameplay or saves. ---

Original mod by Taranchuk. This is a maintained fork with bug fixes and improvements.

===========================

載入畫面讓你等得不耐煩？這款模組就是為此而生。

它透過幾種背景優化手段縮短 RimWorld 的啟動時間，完全不影響遊戲內容與存檔。

--- 功能說明 ---

- 在遊戲啟動的空閒時間提前載入模組內容，減少等待。
- 可選擇延遲載入非必要貼圖（例如背景物件裝飾），等進入遊戲後才處理。武器、服裝、食物、人物、傢俱等必要物品仍會立即載入，不會出現問題。（預設關閉）
- 更聰明的圖集烘焙：預設使用 RimWorld 原版烘焙流程。開啟後會根據你的 GPU 速度自動調整每批次處理量，減少載入卡頓。此功能為可選，模組量大時建議啟用。（預設關閉）
- 貼圖降解析度工具：可縮小高畫質貼圖來節省顯示記憶體與載入時間。原始模組檔案不會被動到——縮小版本存在獨立資料夾，隨時刪除即可還原原始品質。（預設關閉）

--- 注意事項 ---

- 啟動期間遊戲可能短暫無回應，這是正常現象，模組正在背景運作。
- 開啟延遲貼圖載入後，剛進入遊戲時部分物件可能短暫顯示為粉紅色或灰色佔位圖，幾秒後會自動補齊。
- 貼圖降解析工具和圖集烘焙均為可選功能。圖集烘焙在任何情況下都會執行——關閉設定只是改用原版烘焙方式，而非停用烘焙。

--- 推薦搭配使用 ---

- Loading Progress
- DefLoadCache
- Image Opt

--- 模組越多效果越明顯，對遊戲內容與存檔零影響。---

原作者：Taranchuk。此為持續維護的分支版本，包含錯誤修復與功能改進。
  </description>
  <loadBefore>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
  </loadBefore>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>garethp.modlistconfigurator</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>