<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Faster Game Loading - Continued</name>
  <author>綠菇</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>Taranchuk.FasterGameLoading</packageId>
  <modVersion>2026.06.17.7</modVersion>
  <description>
GitHub (Maintained Fork): https://github.com/mushroomTW/FasterGameLoading---Continued
Original Project: https://github.com/Taranchuk/FasterGameLoading

=== Does loading take forever? This mod is for you! ===

Sick of staring at the loading screen every time you start RimWorld? This mod cuts down startup time using several tricks that work in the background, so the game loads faster without changing any gameplay.

--- What it does ---

- Early mod content loading: Starts loading mod content earlier, during moments the game would otherwise sit idle. (enabled by default)
- Multi-threaded preloading: Speeds up XML loading and type resolution by utilizing multiple CPU cores. (enabled by default)
- XPath cache: Caches XML queries during load and safely releases it on main menu initialization to prevent runtime conflicts and free up memory. (enabled by default)
- Delay graphic and icon loading: Delay loading non-essential textures (like background objects) until after you enter a game — weapons, clothing, food, pawns, and furniture are always loaded right away so nothing looks broken. (disabled by default)
- Adaptive atlas baking: Automatically adjusts batch sizes based on your GPU speed and keeps RimWorld 1.6 vanilla atlas pre-inserts intact. (disabled by default)
- Verbose logging: Outputs debug messages to the console. (disabled by default)
- Texture downscaler: Reduces the file size of high-resolution textures to save VRAM and speed up loading. Your original mod files are never touched, downscaled copies are stored in a separate folder, and you can delete them anytime to go back to full quality. (disabled by default)

--- Things to know ---

- The game may briefly freeze or feel unresponsive during startup. This is normal — the mod is doing work in the background.
- It may take a while to get any sound after entering the main menu, which is normal.
- If you are using external texture loaders or image conversion tools like Image Opt, Graphics Settings+, or RimSort (Optimize Texture), this mod's texture downscaler will step aside. (Converting to DDS is actually more efficient and has higher quality than directly downscaled images, so it is recommended to use the texture downscaler only when you cannot use such tools)

--- Works well with ---

- Loading Progress
- Missile Girl - Performance Mod or DefLoadCache (choose one)
- Image Opt
- Graphics Settings+

--- Works best with a lot of mods. Zero impact on gameplay or saves. ---

Original mod by Taranchuk. This is a maintained fork with bug fixes and improvements.

===========================

載入畫面讓你等得不耐煩？這款模組就是為此而生。

它透過幾種背景優化手段縮短 RimWorld 的啟動時間，完全不影響遊戲內容與存檔。

--- 功能說明 ---

- 提早載入模組內容：在遊戲啟動的空閒時間提前載入模組內容，減少等待。（預設開啟）
- 多執行緒預載入：利用多核心 CPU 進行並行 XML 加載和反射解析，大幅縮減加載時間。（預設開啟）
- XPath 快取：在載入時快取 XML 查詢，進入主畫面後徹底釋放記憶體，並防止執行期動態查詢產生的相容性衝突。（預設開啟）
- 延遲圖形和圖示載入：延遲載入非必要貼圖（例如背景物件裝飾），等進入遊戲後才處理。武器、服裝、食物、人物、傢俱等必要物品仍會立即載入，不會出現問題。（預設關閉）
- 自適應圖集烘焙：根據你的 GPU 速度自動調整每批次處理量，並保留 RimWorld 1.6 原版必要圖集插入，減少載入卡頓。（預設關閉）
- 啟用詳細日誌：輸出偵錯訊息至控制台以利排查問題。（預設關閉）
- 縮小紋理工具：可縮小高畫質貼圖來節省顯示記憶體與載入時間。（預設關閉）

--- 注意事項 ---

- 啟動期間遊戲可能短暫無回應，這是正常現象，模組正在背景運作。
- 進入主畫面後會有一小段時間沒有聲音，屬於正常現象。
- 如果有使用 Image Opt、Graphics Settings+ 或 RimSort 的 Optimize Texture 等外部貼圖載入或圖片轉化工具，本模組的貼圖降解析度工具會自動退避（轉換成 DDS 實際上比直接降解析度更有效率且品質更高，所以建議只有在無法使用此類工具時使用貼圖降解析度工具）。

--- 推薦搭配與相容性 ---

- Loading Progress
- Missile Girl - Performance Mod 或 DefLoadCache（二選一）
- Image Opt
- Graphics Settings+

--- 模組越多效果越明顯，對遊戲內容與存檔零影響。---

原作者：Taranchuk。此為持續維護的分支版本，包含錯誤修復與相容性功能改進。
  </description>
  <loadBefore>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
  </loadBefore>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>garethp.modlistconfigurator</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
