<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Faster Game Loading - Continued</name>
  <author>綠菇</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>Taranchuk.FasterGameLoading</packageId>
  <modVersion>2026.07.11.3</modVersion>
  <description>
=== Does loading take forever? This mod is for you! ===

Sick of staring at the loading screen every time you start RimWorld? This mod cuts down startup time using several tricks that work in the background, so the game loads faster without changing any gameplay.

--- What it does ---

- Early mod content loading: Starts loading pending mod content during idle loading gaps before RimWorld's normal ReloadContentInt pass reaches those mods. (enabled by default)
- Multi-threaded preloading: Speeds up XML loading and type resolution by utilizing multiple CPU cores. (enabled by default)
- XPath cache: Caches XML queries during load and safely releases it on main menu initialization to prevent runtime conflicts and free up memory. (enabled by default)
- Delay graphic and icon loading: Delay loading non-essential textures (like background objects) until after you enter a game — weapons, clothing, food, pawns, and furniture are always loaded right away so nothing looks broken. (disabled by default)
- Adaptive atlas baking: Automatically adjusts batch sizes based on your GPU speed and keeps RimWorld 1.6 vanilla atlas pre-inserts intact. (disabled by default)
- Verbose logging: Outputs debug messages to the console. (disabled by default)
- Texture downscaler: Reduces the file size of high-resolution textures to save VRAM and speed up loading. Your original mod files are never touched, downscaled copies are stored in a separate folder, and you can delete them anytime to go back to full quality. (disabled by default)

--- Things to know ---

- The game may briefly freeze or feel unresponsive during startup. This is normal — the mod is doing work in the background.
- It may take a while to get any sound after entering the main menu, which is normal; sound playback is released automatically after deferred sound definitions finish resolving.
- When delay graphic loading is disabled, static atlases are not baked again by the delayed startup cleanup, preventing duplicate atlas VRAM usage with large race or texture-heavy mods.
- ChezhouLib's AssetBundle reload patch runs before FGL's duplicate-reload guard, so ChezhouLib-managed bundles can refresh correctly during development reload paths.
- Early mod content loading now includes official Core/DLC packs as well as player mods.
- If you are using Image Opt, this mod's texture downscaler will step aside, while early content loading remains enabled. Invalid Image Opt .dds / .dds.zstd cache files are cleaned in texture folders only, in the background, so Image Opt can fall back or regenerate cleanly. For Graphics Settings+ or RimSort (Optimize Texture), the texture downscaler will step aside. (Converting to DDS is actually more efficient and has higher quality than directly downscaled images, so it is recommended to use the texture downscaler only when you cannot use such tools)

--- Works well with ---

- Loading Progress
- Missile Girl - Performance Mod or DefLoadCache (choose one)
- Image Opt
- Graphics Settings+

--- Works best with a lot of mods. Zero impact on gameplay or saves. ---

Original mod by Taranchuk. This is a maintained fork with bug fixes and improvements.
  </description>
  <loadBefore>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
  </loadBefore>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>garethp.modlistconfigurator</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
