<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <FGL_ModName>Faster Game Loading - Continued</FGL_ModName>

    <!-- Settings -->
    <FGL_EarlyModContentLoading>Load mod content early during game idling periods. When enabled, the game might become unresponsive during loading, but it's expected. Disable this if you encounter any issues.</FGL_EarlyModContentLoading>
    <FGL_DelayGraphicLoading>Delay graphic and icon loading to game runtime (ADVANCED). This can speed up initial loading, but may cause temporary texture issues. The delayed loading is now optimized for better performance. Only enable if you have many high-resolution texture mods and understand the trade-offs.</FGL_DelayGraphicLoading>
    <FGL_DisableStaticAtlasesBaking>Disable static texture atlas baking (ADVANCED). This can slightly speed up initial loading, but will reduce in-game rendering performance (lower TPS). The atlas system is now optimized to work better with delayed loading. Not recommended unless you experience specific issues.</FGL_DisableStaticAtlasesBaking>

    <!-- Texture Resizing -->
    <FGL_TextureResizingExplanation>Some mods may contain a lot of high-res textures that take a long time to load. Use this to downscale hi-res textures. Original files will NOT be modified; downscaled versions are stored in a separate cache and loaded automatically on next startup. \n
        Following textures will be reduced down to target size: \n
        Building - 256px\n
        Pawn - 256px\n
        Apparel - 128px \n
        Weapon - 128px\n
        Item - 128px\n
        Plant - 128px\n
        Tree - 256px\n
        Terrain - 1024px</FGL_TextureResizingExplanation>
    <FGL_DownscaleTextures>Downscale textures</FGL_DownscaleTextures>
    <FGL_TextureResizingConfirmation>Perform texture downscaling? Downscaled textures will be cached separately; original mod files will not be modified.</FGL_TextureResizingConfirmation>
    <FGL_ClearTextureCache>Clear texture cache</FGL_ClearTextureCache>
    <FGL_ClearTextureCacheConfirmation>Clear all cached downscaled textures? Original textures will be used on next startup.</FGL_ClearTextureCacheConfirmation>
    <FGL_TextureCacheStatus_Active>Texture cache active: {0} textures cached.</FGL_TextureCacheStatus_Active>
    <FGL_TextureCacheStatus_Empty>Texture cache is empty. No textures have been downscaled.</FGL_TextureCacheStatus_Empty>
</LanguageData>
